本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 许块块招不到人悲催包片= =
校对： 许块块   后期： 唱唱反调
这是什么地方
What is this place?
- 我到底怎么了 嘿 嘿 这里...
- What's wrong with me?! - Hey, hey, hey, here...
只是有点恶心 瞧
It's just a little bit of transcendental sickness. Look...
好吧
Okay...
抱歉
Sorry...
那到底是什么东西
What the hell was that?
我刚刚救了你的命
I just saved your life!
像你自己这样非元素的人从这架
Non-Elemental boys like yourself can't pass
飞机到另外一架是肯定会恶心的
from one plane to the next without getting sick.
下一站和上一站是一样的
Next stop same as the last!
上一站和这站也是一样的
Last stop same before next!
请准备好您的票
Get your tickets ready please!
嘿
Hey!
我们在找一个女人 她叫波...
We're looking for a woman. Her name is Bo...
哇呜！
Whoa!
对这些家伙不用担心
Nothing to worry about folks!
工程师肯定忘了他的眼镜
The engineer must have forgotten his glasses!
嘿
Hey!
当提到波的名字时 是我震了下
Is it me or did this entire train just shake
还是整节火车震了下
at the mention of Bo's name?
这诅咒灵魂的尖叫
The screams...
被捕捉到了 他们也正试着逃出来
damned souls are trapped and they're trying to get out.
我们从这逃出来 找到了你的女孩
We gotta get out of here and find your girl.
来吧
Come on.
- 您能停下来吗 - 我讨厌这个地方
- Would you please stop with the attitude? - I hate this place.
这里啥都没有 无线网也没有 这就是一屎坑
There's no WIFI or anything, and it's a shit-hole!
我来这只呆一夜
It's just gonna be for one night.
呆在这
Stay here...
家
Home?
什么 有人已经做过了什么
What? Someone had to do something.
当你不知你是谁时 生活会很艰辛
Life is hard when you don't know who you are.
当你知道真相后 生活会更艰难
It's harder when you don't know what you are.
我的爱伴随死神的降临
My love carries a death sentence.
我迷失了多年
I was lost for years...
在藏匿中找寻
Searching, while hiding.
那个不为人知的属于我的世界
Only to find that I belong to a world hidden from humans.
但我已厌倦躲藏
I won't hide anymore.
我要过自己想要的生活
I will live the life I choose.
左边松 右边紧
Lefty loosey. Righty tighty.
看到你妈妈穿着睡衣在
Seen your mother in her nighty.
问题出在这啊
Oh, there's the little trouble maker.
需要帮助嘛 姑娘
Can I help you, young lady?
你把一架钢琴丢在了波兰 不是吗
You miss the piano that you left back in Poland, don't you?
真遗憾 我本可以让你出名的
Pity. I could have made you a star.
我勒个去
Holy crap!
- 你做了什么 - 稍微整理了下
- What did you do? - A little reorganizing.
- 可以吗 - 可以?
- Is it okay? - Okay?
这里比我那狗窝整齐多了
This place is more organized than my shitty apartment.
嗯... 糖摆在盐和胡椒旁
Um... sugar is with salt and pepper.
显然
Obviously.
好吧 那醋同蕃茄酱和其他调味品在一起
And, um, vinegar is with ketchup and other condiments.
噢 不再跟小苏打放了
Oh! And no longer directly next to the baking soda
你绝对能想到当我看到
... you can imagine my surprise when I saw that ...
这两种东西绝对混合在一起开了个聚会
actually everybody's surprised if those two decide
我和我的小伙伴都惊呆了
to mix it up and have a party.
碳酸实际上是不稳定的
Carbonic acid is actually very unstable ...
有一点像这里...和罗纳德
kind of like this place ... and Ronald.
- 你真滑稽   - 我吗
- You're hilarious. - Am I?
所以呢 你喜欢吗
So? You like?
是的 我太喜欢了
Yeah. I do like.
我要点糖
I just need some sugar.
克里斯朵... 我做不到
Crystal... I can't.
休息结束了
Break's over!
- 休息结束了！！！  - 看到没
- Break's over!!! - See?
太不稳定了
Unstable.
看到了 太好玩了
See. Funny.
- 你刚在火车上吗 - 什么火车
- Were you on the train? - What train?
妈妈 火车很明显是海洛因的另称
Mom... "train" is obviously slang for heroin.
我的意思是 瞧瞧她
I mean, just look at her.
你好 我叫凯西
Hi, my name is Kathy.
这是我的...充满活力的女儿 朱莉安
and this is my... energetic daughter, Julia.
为什么他要那样走路
Why is he walking like that?
那是老金宁思家族的迷信
Oh, it's an old Jenkins family superstition.
- 周末玩的愉快 -  那些烟雾到哪去了
- Makes for a fun weekend. - Where did all the smoke go?
有人把所有的玻璃都打碎了
Somebody broke all those glasses.
- 婊子你脑子是不是坏掉了 - 朱莉安!
- Bitch, I think your brain broke ... - Julia!
这些对劳伦有用吗
Does this have something to do with Lauren?
上帝啊 为什么我记不住呢 我...
Oh, God... why can't I remember, I...
- 有人打我了吗  - 妈妈打的
- Did somebody hit me? - Mom did.
上帝啊
Oh, God...
上帝啊 我太饿了
Oh, God, I am so hungry.
你想吃点什么吗
Would you like something to eat?
求你不要问我吃什么
Oh, please do not ask me that.
把他们都杀了吧 杀了他们...
Kill them... Kill them all...
干掉他们
Kill them.
振作起来啊 丹妮丝
Oh... Keep it together, Dennis.
好吧 鞋子都挂在...
Okay... shoes are all hung...
伊恩... 我们的客人醒了
Ian... our guest is awake.
你不要把我爸当热狗一样看好吗
Uh, can you not look at my Dad like he's made out of hotdogs?
- 小姑娘 - 没事
- Young lady ... - It's okay.
她让我想起我最好的朋友 真舒服
She reminds me of my best friend. It's comforting.
听着 我不想对你粗鲁
Look, I don't mean to be rude,
但是你真的要走了...
but you need to go...
爸爸 她快死了啊 天啊
Dad. She's practically a dead person. Jesus.
她要走了 就现在
She needs to go. Now.
伊恩 她什么都没有
Ian, she hasn't had anything...
女孩们
Girls!!!
就现在
Now!
我能先用下卫生间吗
Can I use the ladies room first?
这是她的房间 她在这
This was her room. She was here.
嘿 起床了啊！
Hey! Wake up!
那个对你做过的女孩...
The girl that did this to you...
她真擅长接吻啊...
She's such a good kisser...
她在哪！ 波在哪
Where is she?! Where's Bo?!
他要是发现她走了 他肯定会疯掉的
He's gonna be so angry when he finds out she's gone...
波!!!
Bo!!!
这是她的
This was hers.
她从这跳下去的痛相比你刚刚的难受
If she jumped from the sickness that you had
那只是冰山一角啊
a minute ago, it's just the tip of the iceberg.
发热和胃痉挛都会导致死亡
The delirium and the stomach cramps are gonna lead to death.
但是我很好啊
But I'm fine!
因为你和我在一起 元素
Because you're with me, an Elemental.
但是这火车太特别了
And this train is special.
如果你没有邀请就离开或者进来的话...
If you leave or enter without an invitation ...
或者只是靠一下
or at least an anchor...
但是你可以救她 不是吗
But you could save her, right?
我不知道 也许吧...
I don't know. Maybe...
你可以的 加油...
You can do this, come on...
系好你的安全带 男孩
Fasten your seat belt, Lover Boy.
你到底在这搞什么
What the hell are you doing down here?
今年还没过很久呢 是吗 伊恩?
Not so much father of the year, are we, Ian?
你认为你可以让别人来违背他们的意愿
You think you can just hold people against their will? Huh?
你要让你的女儿把牢底坐穿
You're keeping your daughter prisoner?
你太不了解我了
You don't know anything about me...
我们正在保护朱莉安
We are protecting Julia.
我不需要你的保护
I don't need you to protect me.
- 保护她干什么 - 一个傻逼幽灵
- Protect her from what? - A stupid ghost!
再来一次
Come again?
我家被鬼缠身了
My family's haunted.
我们都是为每年的今天而来
Every year on this exact day it comes for us.
这就是我为什么要逃出这
That's why we come out here.
我们离开我们的邻居 我们离开我们的家族
We get away from neighbors, we get away from families.
我们把我们锁在这里一直到早晨
We lock ourselves in these cells until morning.
直到消失
Until it's gone.
为什么幽灵会缠住你的家族
Why is a ghost haunting your family?
我不知道 我身上貌似有他们的东西
I don't know. I just inherited the damn thing.
我家里每个人还没有告诉是什么时就死了
Everyone in my family died before they could tell my why.
你知道要想搞定这奇怪的东西是我要做的事情
Well, you know dealing with "weird shit" is kinda what I do.
我能帮助你
I can help.
天啊 帮助啥 哪有什么鬼 你这二货
O-M-G, help what? There is no frigging ghost, you psychos!
每年都会把我锁在这狗屁房间
Every year you lock me up in this stupid house,
我从来没有看见过一次鬼
and I have never even once seen a Ghost!
你休想再把我锁住了
You can't keep jailing me away!
- 好吧 就现在  - 爸爸 不要
- All right, it's time. - Dad! No!
现在是你离开我房间的时候了
And it's time for you to leave my house.
如果我被锁住 她也要被锁住
If I'm locked up ... then she's locked up too.
你们两个不能呆在一起 朱莉安 你懂的
You both can't be in the same cell, Julia. You know that!
伊恩 要是她去外面 过了鞋子结呢?
Ian, what if she goes outside past the shoes and the knots?
我不会拿我女儿命来冒险
I am not risking my daughter's life!
现在你赶紧离开这
And you need to leave now!
- 爸爸 - 好 我就走
- Dad! - It's ok. I'll go.
谢谢你做的一切
Thank you for everything.
在...
In...
好吧
Okay...
没有电话 没有信件 没有任何的回应
No phone calls, no letters. No correspondence of any kind.
五年之类都没有
For five long years.
从现在开始 没有我 你活不下去
And now all of a sudden, you can't live without me.
我能说什么呢 我太感动了
What can I say? I'm touched.
如果生活教会我一件事情
If there's one thing that life has taught me,
那就是没有你 我绝对能活下去
it's that I can definitely live without you.
但是 我同意 你确实被感动了
But, I agree. You are touched.
现在开始 就有些不同了
Now, there is something different about you.
伊娃 你染过头发
Evony. Did you dye your hair?
是的 谢谢你注意到
Yes. Thank you for noticing.
这个颜色叫做把我眼球装回去
The color is called Grow-My-Eyeball-Back-
不然我把你变个球
Or-You-Will-Be-Growing-Back -A-Ball-Of-Your-Own!
- 朗朗上口啊 - 难道不是吗
- That's catchy. - Isn't it just?
是的
Yeah.
你在你的教堂合唱团里唱女高音 不是吗
You sing soprano in your church choir don't you?
是女低音
Alto.
我的孩子
Oh. My child...
我看见你还是可以和你的孩子相处的
I see you still have a way with children.
这职业真危险
Hazard of the profession, I suppose.
你要有我手上的权利
When you've been in power as long as I have ...
谁对你而言都是孩子
everyone is your child.
信不信由你
Like it or not,
某天你一觉醒来 你就成了妈
one day you just wake up and you're a mother.
还有德鲁
And Druid.
别让我失望
Don't disappoint me like 'Chanel Number Goo' did.
- 我的眼睛是棕色的 - 它们有些棕色
- My eyes are brown. - Actually, they're imperial brown
瞳孔又有点发绿色
with a slight flare of green in the rim of the cornea.
别弄砸了
Just don't screw this up.
老爸? 老爸 我错了
Dad? Dad, I'm sorry...
- 嘿 - 你回来了
- Hey... - You came back.
想要个室友吗
Need a cell mate?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
你就像健康课视频里的女孩
You kind of look like that girl from that video
刚刚生完恶心的孩子
in health class giving gross birth.
没事的 肯吉
It's fine, Kenz, really.
谁是肯吉?
Uh, who's Kenz?
肯定是我思念已久的人
Somebody I obviously miss very much.
听着 朱莉安 怎么回事?
Look, um, Julia... What is going on?
我也有过不好的家庭团聚
I've been to my share of bad family reunions,
相信我 这是个疯狂的小镇
believe me, but this is crazy town.
我能给你看个东西吗
Um, can I show you something?
杀了他们 把他们杀光
Kill them... Kill them all
杀了他们
Kill them...
我们家的人 一直都会死
People in my family, keep... they keep dying.
凶杀 自杀
Murder. Suicide.
我的祖父毒死了全家 几乎全家死亡
My great grandfather he poisoned his whole family, almost, and then...
还把他们放在桌旁 开茶会
posed them like dolls that are at a tea party.
还有这里
Um, and then there's...
这个
there's this.
这个小男孩 是我爸爸
That little boy, right there? That's my Dad.
他看见爸爸射杀全家
He saw his father shoot his entire family.
你知道他怎么谈论遗传鬼魂吗?
You know how he talked about inheriting this ghost?
要是他有家族遗传病呢?
What if what he actually inherited is this thing? This...
这迫使他做这些疯狂的举动
...thing that keeps making them do all this horrible stuff.
你还见过更奇怪的吗
You've never seen anything out of the ordinary?
他把我锁在盒子里 好吗 他有病
He locks me in a box, okay? He's sick.
我真害怕有一天他会伤害我们
I'm just scared that one day he's gonna hurt us.
那我无能为力了
Well, I guess there's nothing I can do.
不过可以救你出去
Except get you out of here.
谢谢 谢谢你听我说
Oh, thank you. Thank you for listening to me.
其实你还挺酷的 对一个
You know, for a totally loco chick breaking in our house, you're...
破门而入的流浪女来说
you're actually pretty cool.
来吧
Come on.
我们跟丢了她味道
We've lost her scent.
不不 放心 我认识这片森林
No, no, relax... I know these woods.
我朋友懒约翰被埋在这
My friend Lazy John was buried out here.
我靠着树睡着了 然后
He fell asleep against a tree and then...
- 猴子们把他埋了 - 猴子吗?
- monkeys buried him. - Monkeys?
约翰 约翰
John! John.
约翰
John...
嗨 约翰
Hi, John.
- 你好啊 亲爱的 - 嗨 西里欧
- Hello. Hi, honey. - Hi, Clio.
约翰
John...
见见我的生意伙伴
I would like you to meet my business associate.
- 约翰 - 生意伙伴
- John. - Business Associate.
你看到淫妖穿过树林吗
Have you seen a Succubus running through these woods?
你的淫妖昨晚过去的 不过...
Your Succubus ran through last night. But...
她朝哪个方向走的
what direction did she go? Hm.
好吧
Okay.
不许作评价
Don't judge me.
- 你可以添一只趾头 - 不
- You can lick one toe. - No!
- 要他的 - 什么?
- Him. - Come again?
你想不想找到淫妖了
Do you want to find your Succubus, or not?
生意伙伴
Business associate.
天啊 你也太爱这姑娘了吧
Man! You must really love this girl.
这话题不许再提了
We shall never speak of this again.
这些巫毒术到底是什么故事?
So, what's the real story with this voodoo juju?
显然是笨鬼进不来
Apparently the stupid ghost can't come inside
除非她解开所有的鞋子和扣 弱爆了
'til she tries on all the shoes and unties all the knots; lame!
- 那向后倒呢? - 你向后走
- And walking backwards? - Oh, a ghost can't jump inside your body
鬼就不能附身 还真有道理
if you're walking backwards, duh. 'Cause that makes sense.
那可不是鬼魂
Oh. That's not a ghost.
那是附身鬼啊 朱莉安!
That's a body jumper! Julia!
朱莉安 不
Julia, no!
天啊 你生病了?
Jesus! You're sick?
我让你别掺和
I told you not to interfere!
我很抱歉 我只想帮忙
Look, I'm sorry. I was just trying to help.
帮忙 我已经控制住了
Help?! I had this under control!
伊恩!
Ian!
- 朱莉安在哪倒下的? - 外面
- Where did Julia collapse? - Outside.
鞋子结以外
Past the shoes and knots.
伊恩 你在干嘛
Ian, what are you doing?!
我们曾说过要是我们中有人被附身
We said if this thing entered one of us,
不论谁杀无赦
we would kill whoever that was!
不要杀朱莉安!
But not Julia!
我不会让她活...
I will not let her live...
让她忍受我忍过的一切
with what I had to live with.
伊恩! 求你了 她是我们的孩子
Ian! Please! She's our baby!
我知道你童年发生过的事
I know what happened to you when you were young ...
可这事另有它法
but there is always another way.
你一无所知
You don't know anything!
你不知道它对我家人伤害多大
You don't know what this thing did to my family.
杀了我弟弟 妹妹 妈妈 爸爸
To my brother, to my sister my mother, my father!
- 它指使我做 - 你?
- What it made me do. - You?
你跟我说是你爸做的
You told me that was your father!
要是朱莉安也得做我经历过的事...
If Julia ever had to do what I did...
你不懂它在你体内的感觉
You don't know what it's like to have something inside of you!
让你无法控制
To have something you just can't control.
其实 我懂 我能挽救这一切
Actually, yeah, I do. I can fix this.
挽救?
Fix it?
我手刃全家人之后
I can still hear that thing laughing...
还能听到那玩意的笑声
...while I butchered everybody that I loved.
你不能挽救邪恶
You can't fix pure evil.
他说得对 我就是邪恶
He's right. I am pure evil.
我感觉太好了
And I ain't never felt better.
走 躲起来 我不会让悲剧发生的
Go! Hide! I won't let anything happen!
- 女儿不走我不走 - 我来处理
- Not without our daughter! - I've got this.
快点 走了
Come on, let's go!
小费
Tips.
- 谢谢 - 嗯
- Thanks. - Mm-hmm.
- 我脑子里太乱了 - 没事的 我了解
- I just have a lot on my mind. - It's okay. Really, I get it.
你为什么在这
Why are you here?
- 我在这工作? - 我知道
- Uh... I work here? - Yeah, I know.
可是
It's just that...
我知道为什么罗纳德在这
I know why Ronald is here.
只是我还在回忆为什么我在这
And I'm still kinda working on why I'm here...
原来是这么个意思
Oh, that 'why are you here'.
要是太私人不方便的话...
You know what, if it's too personal a question...
没事的
It's okay.
我想
Uh... well, I guess...
有时 女孩家太不走运
...sometimes when a girl's had so much bad luck...
就觉得自己是一切霉运的起因
she can... start to feel like she's the one causing it.
她就是扫把星
She is bad luck.
那时你也就坦然接受一切了
And that's when you start to except things.
就像是镇里最好的歌手
Like how being the best singer in town
在大城市里一文不值
doesn't really mean very much in the big city.
你若不转换成小的梦想奋斗
And how sometimes big dreams will swallow you whole.
有时大抱负会将你整个吞噬掉
If you don't turn 'em into small ones instead.
像这种小梦想
Small ones like this.
- 出售农场 - 小农场出售
- Farm for sale? - Small farm for sale.
不到十英亩
Just under ten acres.
一群鸡和猪
Couple of chickens. Pigs.
一只叫公爵的巴洛米诺马
An old Palomino named Duke.
辛苦劳作一天 夜晚静坐下来看星星
Work hard all day and just sit and watch the stars at night.
宛若天堂
Little heaven right there.
- 明天见 - 嗯
- See you tomorrow. - Mm-hmm.
我知道你不想谈恋爱
Listen, I know you're not on the market
可要想找人喝点酒
but if you ever wanna grab some beer and...
吃点披萨 吐露心声
a pizza and vent...
- 你知道我在哪 - 我根本不知道你住哪
- you know where I live. - I have no idea where you live.
你究竟是什么东西
What the hell are you?
两条腿的奇人
Awesome on two legs.
你是什么异种
And what type of Fae might you be?
受死 受死 受死吧
Jumbee,  Jumbee, Jumbee, Jumbee....
我不想伤害你朱莉安 可这婊子宁死不屈啊
Oh, I don't want to hurt you Julia, but this bitch ain't making it easy.
啊 你他妈是谁
Ahhhh! Who the hell are you?
戴森
Dyson!
他叫戴森 没事的
His name is Dyson. It's okay.
天啊 你怎么找到我的
Oh, God... how did you find me?
我找人帮忙了
I had a little help.
受死 受死 受死吧
Jumbee, Jumbee, Jumbee, Jumbee...
波 这位是西里欧
Bo, meet Clio.
啤酒 披萨 吐露心声
The beer and the pizza and the venting.
现在有点太快了吗
Is right now too soon?
当然不
Of course not.
进来吧
Come on in.
我知道你能附身 你还有什么本事
We know you can body-jump, but what else you got?
我刚刚同意3P了吗
Huh... did I just agree to a threesome?
妈妈 他们在伤害我
Mama! Mama, they're hurting me!
- 宝贝 - 妈
- Baby! - Mom!
凯西 不要
Kathy, no!!!
凯西
Kathy!!!
不 天啊
No... Oh, God...
- 天啊 - 芍药
- Oh, God... - The Peony plant.
什么
What?
能止血 是医治神的草药
It's gonna stop the bleeding. It's healing plant of the Gods.
- 在森林里有 - 快去
- It grows in the forest. - Go!
好的
Okay.
波 我要救你出去
Bo... I've got to get you out of here.
- 你快死了 - 这女人才快死了
- You're dying. - This woman is dying.
你不懂 当你从那火车
You don't understand. When you jumped from
跳下来的时候 你就病了 你需要帮助
that train, you got sick. You need help.
她需要帮助 戴森 这是我的错
She needs help, Dyson. And it's my fault!
帮我解决 好吗 我能等
Help me fix this, okay? I can wait.
- 紧压伤口 - 去啊 找到我的朱莉安!
- Just keep pressure on the wound. - Go! Get my Julia!
- 我不能失去她们俩 - 啊
- I can't lose them both! - Ah!
垂死之际 还在帮助人类
On death's door, and still helping humans...
至少你还是你
at least you're still you.
清醒 保持清醒 清醒
Stay with me... stay with me, stay with me...
天啊
Oh, man.
为什么我们不能消除一切
Why can't we just.... erase everything.
一切我们身上发生过的糟糕事
All the bad shit that's ever happened to us,
我们做过的事 能不能忘记 忘却一切
or that we've done. and just forget it ... all.
忘记饥渴的老板 乱摸我屁股
Forget that horny boss that kept grabbing my ass.
忘却我大一新生时期
Forget the wedding dress and combat boots
一整年穿婚纱和军靴
that I wore all the way through freshmen year
- 是种宣告 - 是啊 忘记吧
- ... as a "statement." - Yeah. Forget that...
忘却我撞的车 之后逃逸
forget that car that I hit and then sped away,
直到现在前 没告诉过任何人
and didn't tell anyone. Until now.
- 其实撞了三辆 - 什么
- Actually it was three. - What?
- 继续啊 - 好的 好的
- Go, go! - Okay, okay, okay!
忘却用合同束缚我的主人
Uh, forget the Master I had for five years
我为他卖命了五年
who kept me in indentured servitude...
什么
What?
酒后胡言罢了 我想我没什么吐槽的了
It's probably the beer talking. I guess I ran out of bad shit to forget.
想想我们真的能忘掉这一切
Imagine we could really forget all of that stuff ...
我们还剩什么
what would we have left?
天啊
Oh, my God...
我有酒有披萨就够了 好吗
You know, I would have been fine with just beer and pizza, right?
倒轮你来说教
Now she tells me.
什么计划啊
So, what's the plan?
是时候让我见识见识这个受死精了
It's time for me to introduce myself to this Jumbee.
等等
Wait...
- 你 - 你不该那么做的
- you? - You shouldn't have done that.
不关你的事 你真不该瞎掺和
You shouldn't be meddling in things that don't concern you!
显然 你已经不在这世界上很多年了
Clearly, you haven't been out in the world
让我来帮你赶上进度吧
for a while, so let me get you up to speed.
嘿 我是波 无帮派的淫妖 你好吗
Hi, I'm Bo, the unaligned Succubus, how are you?
简单介绍我下 我喜欢皮制品和享乐
A couple things about me ... I like leather, having a good time,
以防你还没注意到
and in case you haven't noticed ...
我一直都掺和与我无关的事
I always meddle in things that don't concern me.
你要是能停止玩弄无辜的人
And if you don't stop torturing these innocent people
我立刻就抽身离开
I'm gonna crack my foot off in your retro ass!
玩弄他们
Torturing them!?
他们以为我是女巫
They thought I was a witch.
嘿嘿 拜托 孩子们 我们谈过了
Hey, hey... come on, boys, we talked about this...
你放开她 别伤害她
Take your hands off her! Don't you hurt her!
你放开我 让她走
Get your hands off me! Let her go!!!
约翰! 杰西!
John! Jesse!
诺亚!!!
Noah!!!
他们想要我的未婚夫诺亚 见证我是女巫
And they wanted my fianc? my Noah, to see me proved a witch.
别这么做
Don't do this!!!
求你们了
Please!
元素不是女巫
An Elemental ain't no witch!
诺亚看到我是什么 他依旧爱我
My Noah saw what I really was and he still loved me.
不
No!
他们让我们永远分开
They left us separate forever.
除非金宁思家死绝
And I ain't never gonna stop until every last one
我绝不罢手
of them Jenkins' is dead!
他们杀了她 你的祖先杀了她
They killed her. Your ancestors killed her.
她和她的未婚夫 金宁思的 杀了她
Her and her fianc? also a Jenkins, murdered her!
天啊 怨恨深重啊
Oh, God! So much anger!
苦难难敌 她永不会收手的
So much pain! She's never gonna stop!
为什么要让我们来还债
Why are they making me pay for what they did??
- 因为因果报复循环 - 她要掌控一切了
- Because the past always comes calling. - She's trying to take over!
跟她打 波
Fight her, Bo!
不错嘛 人类
Not bad. For a human.
我永远任你派遣
Well, I am always at your disposal.
派遣? 我喜欢
Disposal? I like that.
那是什么意思
What was that?
当我在伐克斯桌后的箱子里
When I was in the cell behind Vex's desk,
我有很多时间思考
I had a lot of time to think.
我意识到很重要的事
I realized something very important.
你意识到什么
Oh? What did you realize?
我这人太和善
That I've been far too nice.
我知道淫妖从我手中逃出
I know that Succubus was somehow behind my capture.
是时候有人捉她归位了
It's time somebody finally put her in her place.
我已经做了
I already did.
什么
Excuse me?
她死了 我帮塔米辛摆脱了她
She's gone. I helped Tamsin get rid of her.
为了你 我一直在想
For you. You know, I've been thinking,
也许我该回来
maybe I should come back here.
我和你又能住一起了
I could live here with you again.
亲爱的
Oh... honey...
可是我在哪养狗啊
but then where would I keep the dogs?
你现在要做什么
What are you gonna do now?
既然波死了?
With Bo gone?
无恶不作啊
Everything.
- 永远分开 - 什么
- Separate forever! - What?
永远分离 那就是受死精说的
Separate forever. That's what the Jumbee said!
我知道我们要做什么了
I know what we have to do!
在他们结婚前被杀了
Before they were married, they were killed!
他们分开葬的
They were buried separately!
- 要是我们 - 要是我们怎样
- If we... - If we what?
不不 我知道
No, no, I know!
如果我们把他们合葬
If we bury them together then it will end
受死精就能瞑目了
the Jumbee's need for vengeance.
拜托 你已经千年高寿
Come on, you've been around for a thousand years,
难道就不能读本浪漫小说?
and you've never read a romance novel?
你真是个幸运的姑娘
Wow, you are a lucky girl.
把凯西带到楼下 把你们锁起来
Take Kathy downstairs and lock yourselves up.
好好的 好吗?
Be okay, okay?
戴森 你得去找他们的墓地 好吗
Dyson, you have to go find their remains, ok?
快去啊
Just please hurry.
我不会离开你的 波 我刚找到你
I'm not leaving you, Bo! I just found you!
我绝不可能
There's no way in hell I'm...
- 你相信我吗 - 是的
- Do you trust me? - Yes.
那就相信吧 我能跟她斗争 戴森 你得走了
Then trust this. I can fight her, Dyson, but you have to go.
要快点 求你了 走啊
You have to hurry! Please, just go!
这是他腿骨还是受死精的腿骨啊?
Ok, is this his leg bone or the Jumbee's leg bone?
没关系 反正都要放一起
Doesn't matter. It's all going in the same place.
你跟波都这样约会吗?
Is this how your dates with Bo usually go?
挖坟 救凡人性命?
Digging up graves, and trying to save human lives?
我要说不是 肯定是在撒谎
I'd be lying if I said this didn't have some semblance of nostalgia.
好嘞 她跟他的部分都在一起了?
Okay, that's it... are all of his bits with her bits?
- 是的 没错 - 是吗?
- Yeah, they are. - Yeah?
帮我制服她
Help me hold her down.
- 把你们都杀掉 我太开心了 - 稳住她
- Oh, I'm gonna enjoy killing you both. - Hold her still...
他们从未结婚 因此她不能瞑目
They were never married! That's why she's still stuck in limbo.
如果我们让他们成婚 就会结束痛苦
If we marry them ... maybe it will end the pain...
你在哪找到的
Where did you find these?
我愿娶你做我的合法妻子
I take you to be my lawfully wed wife
无论健康或疾病 死亡也不能
to have and hold, in sickness and in health,
将我们分开
and even in death.
- 你愿意当我的妻子 - 诺亚
- Do you take me to be your... - Noah...
你愿意让诺亚做你的丈夫吗
Do you take Noah to be your lawfully wedded husband?
无论健康或患病 死亡也不能
To have and to hold, in sickness and in health,
将你们分开?
even in death?
我愿意
Yes. I do.
你们在看什么啊?
What are you guys looking at?
你看不到他们?
You can't see them?
等等
Wait...
- 我们? - 准备好回家了?
- Are we? - Ready to go home?
- 当然 - 是啊
- Oh, hells yes. - Yeah.
- 早上好 罗尼! - 接下电话 好吗
- Good morning, Ronny! - Grab the phone, would ya?
有些人每隔十分钟就打来
Some yahoo's been calling every ten minutes or so,
- 询问凯伦- 什么
- asking about some Karen. - What?
说是重金悬赏信息
Yeah. Said there's a big reward for information.
打扰我做准备工作
Hardly had time to do my prep.
你要接吗 红发妹子?
You gonna answer it, Red?
我着急去洗手间
I actually have to go to the washroom.
你的拳脚了得啊
Uh, your kicks are gone all ghetto.
你想借我的猫咪高跟飞靴吗
Oh, you want to borrow my kitten heel fly boots.
它们太美了 也许会让
They are tris gorge and they might make
你这身流浪汉造型
this, um, homeless-persons- nighty-thing you're rockin'
增加点时尚元素
look like an actual fashion choice.
你知道为什么我明白你会好好的吗
You know how I know you're gonna be okay?
因为你和我最好的朋友一样勇敢
Because you've got balls as big as my best friend.
- 她是个姑娘 - 哦
- Who is a girl? - Oh...
再见了 宝贝 别太为难他们
Bye, babe. And don't be so hard on them.
有朝一日 你也会面对自己的恶魔
One day you might have to face down your own demons...
这就能派上用场
and they might come in handy.
要是需要我 就来找我吧
But if you do ever need me... come find me.
- 我要走了 - 什么
- I need to leave. - What?
小镇 我要离开小镇了
Town. I need to leave town.
你在说什么 什么时候走
What are you talking about?? Leave when?
现在 我真不能解释
Now! I can't really explain...
我跟你一起走 好吗 我能帮忙
I... will come with you, ok? I can help ...
不 答应我 要是有人找我
No! Just promise me. If anybody comes looking for me,
你要假装从不认识我
you'll pretend that you never knew me.
- 你去哪 别... - 答应我
- Where are you going? Just... - Promise me.
保证
Promise.
致幸运 我希望你很快能找到好运
For luck. I really hope you find some soon.
等等 还有其他办法离开这吗?
Wait, wait, wait... is there another way out of here?
是啊 快走
Yeah. Come on.
都是生病的人 还这么着急?
You're in an awful rush for a sick girl?
我等不及要爬上床了
I just can't wait to get into bed.
要事第一
First thing's first.
西里欧 你想听听看吗?
Clio ... you wanna do that ear thing?
你以为自己在做什么
What do you think you're doing?
拿走属于自己的东西
Taking what's mine.
有钱能使鬼推磨 你哥们
Money talks, and your buddy,
伐克斯 可有不少钱
Vex, has got boat loads of it.
你真以为你能跟她走吗
Do you really think you're just gonna walk away with her?
这么说吧 你要是跟着我们 或者想阻止我们
Let me put it this way. If you follow us or try to stop me,
我会让异常的痛苦
then I'm gonna let the transcendental sickness
在她体内侵蚀她 然后我会离开她
eat her insides and then I'm gonna leave her
让她身处淫妖的水深火热吧
in a hot and bloody succubus mess.
我不是说逃离我
I don't mean walk away from me.
- 我是说逃离她 - 什么
- I mean walk away from her. - What?
如果我记得没错 受死精也是元素
Last time I checked, Jumbees were Elementals, too.
西里欧 助人为乐终有善报
See, that's the thing about helping people, Clio.
有时因果报复会找上门啦
Sometimes you get paid back with a little thing called Karma.
受死精治愈了我
Jumbee already healed me ...
当她在你体内时 看清了你的图谋
and when she was inside of you she saw exactly what you were up to.
这只是专业...
This is just professional...
你知道我有多累多讨厌
Do you have any idea how sick and tired I am
被人两面三刀欺骗 愚弄玩耍
of being double crossed and lied to and generally dicked around!
你惹错人了
You picked the wrong girl to screw over.
我这人记仇 记私仇
Because I like to make everything personal.
- 你是什么 - 她是噩梦
- What are you? - She's your worst nightmare.
带着微笑死去
Dying with a smile...
这对你来说命太好了
that is much too good a fate for you.
你离开的时候 有点中世纪的感觉?
Did you get a little medieval while you were away?
我不知道 也许吧
I don't know? Maybe.
- 噢 - 嘿
- Oh... - Hey...
那么 伐克斯哈
So... Vex, huh?
- 天啊 他已经选边站了? - 你还说呢
- Man, can that guy pick a team already? - You're one to talk.
天啊 我想你
God, I missed you.
我也想你
I missed you too.
带我回家?
Take me home?
- 没问题 - 好嘞
- You got it. - Yeah.
我等不及见大家了
Hmm. I can't wait to see everyone.
肯吉和黑尔...
Kenzi and Hale...
特里克和...
Trick and...
你知道 有朝一日 我们会谈到
You know, some day we're gonna have to talk
火车上发生的一切
about what happened on that train.
什么火车
What train?
我不知道 我不知道为什么这么说
I don't know. I don't know why I said that...
别担心
Don't worry.
无论怎样 我会弄清楚发生什么事的
I will figure out what happened to me. One way or another.
你就等好吧
You can be sure of that.
我甩不掉你了 是吗
I'm not gonna get rid of you, am I?
可没那么简单 进来吧 搭档
Not that easy, hop in, partner.
你猜怎么着
You know what?
我真高兴见到你
I am really happy to see you.
- 我真的很抱歉 - 为什么
- And I'm really sorry. - Why?
要不要我们停下 看是否需要帮助?
You think we should stop and see if they need help?
抱歉 波 要带你回家了
Sorry, Bo... gotta get you home.
不管是谁 他们都能照顾好自己
Whoever that is can fix their own flat tire.